this exercise asks
us to write some code that calculates
the squares of
three float numbers and we're going to
output the result of those calculations
so a float is just a number with a
decimal value
and we can get the square of any number
by multiplying it by itself
let's run our code
and there's the square of 4.3
now an alternative way to calculate the
square of a number
is with the following syntax four point
three
to the power of two
you can see that we achieve the same
result
so we need to calculate the square of
three different float numbers
and we do that on lines one through
three
and our code runs successfully
you